come back to my channel I
lomom Beau the
[Music]
walk okay
up
[Music]
seconds
okay
okay LOM
collab Insurance products IC Lombard
General insurance insurance
productsc
Insurance Company
liit I partnership with
insurance
of
insurance will be able to access a wide
range of insurance products
insurance
IC L
Insurance home
insur insurance
insurance strategic partnership
comprehensive product portfolio of IC
Lombard
wi
ofcy
comprehensive accessible Insurance
Solutions for indan customers
customers accessible
Insurance lomard General Insurance
company press
releas following the announcement the
shares of policy bazarte limited EB F
limited gained
3.5% to reach 52 week high of
1,330 per pie shares of policy Bazar
liit ,
330 the stock PA some some of the gains
to close session 1.4% higher
at
[Music]
0.5 Reta and government
business a
second
alicious occasion of g p uh we are
pleased to join forces with policy
basar aim to democrati Insurance in
India by offering customers an
accessible and comprehensive platform to
purchase insurance
seamlessly cons consumers accessible and
insurance LOM General
Insurance
comprehensive LOM has issued more
than
million
claims along with having a gross return
premium gross
return
[Music]
2772 for final year
20234 premium gross return
[Music]
premiums
Rel
hello kuk Fabrications
hello hi
[Music]
okays sorry number uh sorry
number
Med
subcribers family
members
Okay
C Insurance
products
[Music]
so bye
everyone